const questions = [
    {
      question: "What does DSWA stand for?",
      options: ["Dry Stone Walling Association", "Dry Stone Walling Advanced", "Dry Stone Wallers Association", "Dry Stone Wall Association"],
      correctAnswer: "Dry Stone Walling Association"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the top DSWA level?",
      options: ["Master Craftsmen", "Master Waller", "Top Dog", "Master Crafter"],
      correctAnswer: "Master Craftsman"
    },
    {
      question: "A stone which is lengthways along the face of the wall is called?",
      options: ["Traced", "Length In", "Through", "Fill"],
      correctAnswer: "Traced"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a common name for the walls top stones?",
        options: ["Copes", "Hats", "Lids", "Tops"],
        correctAnswer: "Copes"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of these is NOT a name for small stones used to support the wall?",
        options: ["Fill", "Hearting", "Packing", "Stuffing"],
        correctAnswer: "Stuffing"
      },
      {
        question: "What are the foundation stones also called?",
        options: ["Footings", "Floors", "Bottoms", "Bases"],
        correctAnswer: "Footings"
      },
      {
        question: "What is the primary material used in dry stone walling?",
        options: ["Wood", "Metal", "Stone", "Rocks"],
        correctAnswer: "Stone"
      },
      {
        question: "What do you call a wall that uses no mortar?",
        options: ["Dry Stone", "Wet Stone", "Dried Stone", "Mortarless"],
        correctAnswer: "Dry Stone"
      },
      {
        question: "What do you call the side of the stone looking outwards from the wall?",
        options: ["Face", "Head", "Traced", "Outer"],
        correctAnswer: "Face"
      },
      {
        question: "Whats the average dry stone wall height?",
        options: ["9-10ft", "1-2ft", "3-5ft", "2-3ft"],
        correctAnswer: "3-5ft"
      },
      {
        question: "Which tool is essential for shaping stones in dry stone walling?",
        options: ["Crowbar", "Chisel", "Trowel", "Saw"],
        correctAnswer: "Chisel"
      },
      {
        question: "What do you call a stone that is the length of the wall's thickness?",
        options: ["Through", "Copes", "Traced", "Face"],
        correctAnswer: "Through"
      },
      {
        question: "What is the purpose of the batter in dry stone walling?",
        options: ["Decorative", "Stability", "Ease of construction", "Weather resistance"],
        correctAnswer: "Stability"
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the horizontal layers in a dry stone wall?",
        options: ["Courses", "Levels", "Rows", "Tiers"],
        correctAnswer: "Courses"
      },
      {
        question: "In dry stone walling, what is a cheek end?",
        options: ["Long stone", "A tool", "Wall end", "Wall joint"],
        correctAnswer: "Wall end"
      },
      {
        question: "What do you call a wall built with two faces and a filled core?",
        options: ["Double wall", "Single wall", "Solid wall", "Core wall"],
        correctAnswer: "Double wall"
      },
      {
        question: "What kind of stone is suitable for dry stone walling?",
        options: ["Round stone", "Flat stone", "Irregular stone", "Any"],
        correctAnswer: "Any"
      },
      {
        question: "Approximately how many years old is Skara Brae?",
        options: ["5000", "2000", "1000", "3000"],
        correctAnswer: "5000"
      },
      {
        question: "A small stone used to level or support a larger stone is called?",
        options: ["Pin", "Button", "Slip", "Tiers"],
        correctAnswer: "Pin"
      },
      {
        question: "What do you call a wall made with a single width stack of stones?",
        options: ["Double wall", "Single wall", "Solid wall", "Core wall"],
        correctAnswer: "Single wall"
      },
  ];

  export { questions };